quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What is Python?",
        "choices": [ "A high-level programming language", "A type of snake", 
                "A programming language", "A programming framework"],
        "answer": "A high-level programming language"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which symbol is used for comments in Python?",
        "choices":["//", "--", "#", "/**/"],
        "answer": "#"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following data types is immutable in Python?",
        "choices": ["List", "Set", "Dictionary", "Tuple"],
        "answer": "Tuple"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following statements is used to exit from a loop in Python?",
        "choices": ["Break", "Continue", "Exit", "Stop"],
        "answer": "Break"
    },
    {
    "question":"Which method is used to remove the last element from a list in Python?",
    "choices": ["pop()", "remove()", "del()", "clear()"],
    "answer": "pop()"
    },
]

quiz_data2 = [
    {
        "question":"Which statement is used to define a function in Python?",
    "choices": ["func", "define", "def", "function"],
    "answer": "def"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is NOT a valid Python data structure?",
    "choices": ["List", "Tuple", "Stack", "Dicitonary"],
    "answer": "Stack"
    },
    {
        "question":"What does the input() function do in Python?",
    "choices": ["Prints a message to the console", " Reads input from the user", 
     "Converts a string to an integer", "Generates random numbers"],
    "answer": "Reads input from the user"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is NOT a valid Python operator?",
    "choices": ["+", "-", "*", "/"],
    "answer": "/"
    },
    {
      "question":"Which of the following is NOT a valid Python data type?",
    "choices": ["String", "Integer", "Float", "Boolean"],
    "answer": "Boolean"  
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is NOT a valid Python loop?",
    "choices": ["While", "For", "Do-While", "Foreach"],
    "answer": "Do-While"
    },
]
